Kouki-kun!
Let's go!
Just a little longer!
It's time to go to sleep.
But I don't want to sleep.
Kouki-kun, let's go.
So, ready to go home?
Go ahead!
Don't think it's a good idea to come with us?
A good idea?
Can we stop somewhere?
Okay.
Let's stop this. You're heavy!
Don't let me fall!
Is there a fish tank in your home?
No, but we have a bath!
Don't use that!
When you get home, you have to put it in a water bucket!
Why?
You need to calmly ease it into the water.
Rin-chan.
Don't move.
Look.
Hey, let's go!
Don't let me fall!
Shall we go?
It's here.
It's a river!
I'm going too!
I didn't know that there was a place like this here.
It's Rin's first time here too?
Yeah.
This is my first summer with her.
It's dark. I can't see anything.
Daikichi, teach us!
This way, this way.
Let's go.
Wait!
It's night.
I wanted to play more.
Someone looks tired.
So Kouki, now we go this way.
Good night.
See ya.
Ready to go?
You're standing on your tiptoes.